- Oh, hey, Leonard.
- Good afternoon, Penny.
(Leonard:)So, hi, hey. Uh...
(Leonard:)I was wondering
if you had plans for dinner.
Uh, you mean, dinner tonight?
(Leonard:)There is an inherent ambiguity
in the word "dinner."
(Leonard:)Technically,
it refers to the largest meal of the day.
(Leonard:)So to clarify here,
by dinner, I mean supper.
- Supper?
- Or dinner, you know.
I was thinking 6:30 if you can go,
or a different time.
Uh, 6:30 is great.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Penny:)- Great.
- Yeah, I like hanging out with you guys.
(Leonard:)Us guys?
Oh, you know, Sheldon, Howard, Raj.
Who all is coming?
(Leonard:)They...
(Leonard:)...might all be there.
(Leonard:)Or a subset of them might be there.
(Leonard:)Algebraically speaking,
there are too many unknowns.
(Leonard:)For example,
Sheldon had Quizno's for lunch.
(Leonard:)Sometimes he finds that filling,
other times he doesn't.
It's no fault of Quizno's.
They have a varied menu.